{
    "subject": "resource/Herbert_Spencer",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Jean-Baptiste_Lamarck",
    "human_readable": "Herbert Spencer was influenced by Jean-Baptiste Lamarck.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9630247354507446,
            "question": "What impact did Jean-Baptiste Lamarck's work have on Herbert Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9596492648124695,
            "question": "In what field were both Herbert Spencer and Jean-Baptiste Lamarck influential?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9287052154541016,
            "question": "Can you name some of the ideas that Herbert Spencer adopted from Jean-Baptiste Lamarck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157940149307251,
            "question": "Who influenced Herbert Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8777953386306763,
            "question": "Can you describe the relationship between Herbert Spencer and Jean-Baptiste Lamarck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848690927028656,
            "question": "Are there any known disagreements between the theories of Herbert Spencer and Jean-Baptiste Lamarck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7965987920761108,
            "question": "What other thinkers might have been influenced by Jean-Baptiste Lamarck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6137887835502625,
            "question": "What is Jean-Baptiste Lamarck known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45545634627342224,
            "question": "Was Herbert Spencer a follower of scientific theories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4525323212146759,
            "question": "How did Jean-Baptiste Lamarck's work contribute to the development of evolutionary theory?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Herbert Spencer was influenced by Jean-Baptiste Lamarck.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7349_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Herbert Spencer a follower of scientific theories?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7349_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jean-Baptiste Lamarck known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7349_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other thinkers might have been influenced by Jean-Baptiste Lamarck?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7349_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7349_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. The documents mention that Herbert Spencer developed an all-embracing conception of evolution as the progressive development of the physical world, biological organisms, the human mind, and human culture and societies, which is similar to Jean-Baptiste Lamarck's ideas on evolution. Additionally, the documents state that Spencer relied on Lamarck's discredited theories in his own work. This suggests that Spencer was influenced by Lamarck's ideas on evolution."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Herbert Spencer was influenced by Jean-Baptiste Lamarck. Specifically, the document with the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7349/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt` mentions that \"Herbert Spencer (1820\u20131903) made Lamarck's views popularly known during the nineteenth century,\" indicating an influence of Lamarck on Spencer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}